

Moisés Zambrano

Frontend Web Developer

- mozzes-dev.netlify.app
- +58 4123500712
- github.com/WinFlix

About me

I am 19 years old, I am a Web Developer for 8 months. Always interested in innovating cognitively and standing out for my efficiency in stressful situations.

I am especially interested in current technologies and their development along with visual approaches in user interfaces.

Languages

Spanish · native

English · medium

Interests

Hiking, Sports, Music Technology.

Experience

Logo Designer Independent

International 2019 - 2020

Web E-Commerce

AlingDesign

Netherlands Jan 2021 - Mar 2021

Landing Page Independent

International April 2021 - May 2021

- Initial draft with traditional style.
- Layout and color palette design.
- Digitization in Vectors (Illustrator) and export to different formats.
- Model design and layout and practical implementation.
- Work from the frontend with ReactJS and StyledComponents.
- Implementation of the Server and Database with Firebase.
- API development with NodeJS, Express and Axios.
- Logo design and color structure
- Implementation of copywriting and content unification
- Structuring with HTML5 and complete styles of the page with CSS3

Training

2019/2022 Systems engineer student

Universidad de Margarita

2021 Master of Web Development

Udemy

2022 ReactJS Free Course*

youtube.com/midudev

2022 Bootcamp Full Stack Free*

youtube.com/midudev

Knowledge

JavaScript

HTML

CSS

ReactJS

SEO

Performance